Finding Aid for the SOUL Publications, Inc. records PASC-M.0342
UCLA Library Special Collections
- 1. SOUL Issues, 1966-1982
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 10, Number 19, 1976 January 5 (Box 10, Folder 5)
    "Bill Cosby raps on Xmas, family & fans"
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 10, Number 20 (Box 10, Folder 6)
    "Stevie Wonder: what's he up to now?"
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 10, Number 21, 1976 February 2 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 10, Number 22, 1976 February 16 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Soul (WLIB Edition), Volume 10, Number 23 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Soul (WLIB Edition), Volume 10, Number 24, 1976 March 15 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 10, Number 25, 1976 March 29 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 10, Number 26 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    "Final look at Florence Ballard/original Supremes mourn Florence"
  - Soul, Volume 10, Number 27, 1976 April 26 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Soul, Volume 11, Number 2, 1976 May 10 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    "Michael raps about J-5 changes"
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 11, Number 3 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    "Smokey Robinson special"
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 11, Number 4, 1976 June 7 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Soul (KDIA, WLIB, WVON), Volume 11, Number 5, 1976 June 21 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    10th anniversary issue
  - Soul, Volume 11, Number 6 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Soul, Volume 11, Number 7, 1976 July 19 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Soul (WLIB Edition), Volume 11, Number 8, 1976 August 2 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Soul (WLIB Edition), Volume 11, Number 9 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Soul (WLIB Edition), Volume 11, Number 10 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 11, Number 11, 1976 September 13 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Soul (WLIB Edition), Volume 11, Number 12, 1976 September 27 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Soul, Volume 11, Number 13 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 11, Number 14 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 11, Number 15, 1976 November 8 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 11, Number 16, 1976 November 22 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Soul (WLIB Edition), Volume 11, Number 18 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 11, Number 19 (Box 11, Folder 5)
    "The Jacksons"
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 11, Number 19, 1977 January 3 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 11, Number 20, 1977 January 17 (Box 11, Folder 7)
    "Appealing to cult audiences" [George Clinton/Parliament, Gil Scott-Heron, Labelle]
  - Soul, Volume 11, Number 21 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 11, Number 22, 1977 February 14 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 11, Number 23, 1977 February 28 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Soul (WLIB Edition), Volume 11, Number 24 (Box 11, Folder 11)
    "Special: TV history is made 'Roots' captures America"
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 11, Number 25, 1977 March 28 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 11, Number 26, 1977 April 11 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 12, Number 1 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 12, Number 2, 1977 May 9 (Box 11, Folder 15)
    "Aretha evaluates Aretha with comments by Chaka Khan, Miles Davis and Quincy Jones"
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 12, Number 3, 1977 May 23 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 12, Number 4 (Box 11, Folder 17)
    "Does disco music lead to sex?"
  - Soul (WLIB, WVON, KDIA), Volume 12, Number 5, 1977 June 20 (Box 11, Folder 18)
    11th anniversary issue
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 12, Number 6 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 12, Number 7 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 12, Number 8, 1977 August 1 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 12, Number 9, 1977 August 15 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 12, Number 10 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Soul, Volume 12, Number 11 (Box 11, Folder 24)
    "Exclusive interview: Michael Jackson clears up the rumors"
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 12, Number 12, 1977 September 26 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 12, Number 13, 1977 October 10 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 12, Number 14 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 12, Number 15, 1977 November 7 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 12, Number 16, 1977 November 21 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Soul (WLIB Edition), Volume 12, Number 17 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Soul, Volume 12, Number 18 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Soul, Volume 12, Number 19, 1978 January 2 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 12, Number 20, 1978 January 16 (Box 12, Folder 8)
    "Janet Jackson: making it on her own"
  - Soul, Volume 12, Number 21 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Soul (WLIB Edition), Volume 12, Number 22, 1978 February 13 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Soul (THE KAT Edition), Volume 12, Number 23, 1978 February 27 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 12, Number 24 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Soul (WLIB Edition), Volume 12, Number 25 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 12, Number 26, 1978 April 10 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Soul (THE KAT Edition), Volume 13, Number 1, 1978 April 24 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Soul (WLIB Edition), Volume 13, Number 2 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 13, Number 3 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Soul (WVON, WLIB, KDIA), Volume 13, Number 4, 1978 June 5 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    12th anniversary issue
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 13, Number 5, 1978 June 19 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 13, Number 6 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Soul, Volume 13, Number 7, 1978 July 17 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 13, Number 8, 1978 July 31 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Soul (THE KAT Edition), Volume 13, Number 9 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 13, Number 10 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Soul (THE KAT Edition), Volume 13, Number 11, 1978 September 4 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Soul (THE KAT Edition, Volume 13, Number 12, 1978 September 18 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 13, Number 13 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Soul, Volume 13, Number 14 (Box 13, Folder 11)
    "Mick Jagger on Black girls, Black music, and the Black woman who claims he fathered her child"
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 13, Number 15, 1978 October 30 (Box 13, Folder 12)
    "Special 'Wiz' edition"
  - Soul, Volume 13, Number 16, 1978 November 13 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Soul (THE KAT Edition), Volume 13, Number 17 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Soul, Volume 13, Number 18, 1978 December 11 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 13, Number 19, 1978 December 25 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 13, Number 20 (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - Soul (WVON Edition), Volume 13, Number 21 (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - Soul, Volume 13, Number 22, 1979 February 5 (Box 13, Folder 19)
    "Don't fake the funk!" [Special funk issue with George Clinton, Funkadelic, Sly Stone, Bootsy Collins, James Brown]
  - Soul, Volume 13, Number 23, 1979 February 22 (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - Soul, Volume 13, Number 24 (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - Soul, Volume 13, Number 25, 1979 March 19 (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - Soul (KAT Edition), Volume 13, Number 26, 1979 April 2 (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - Soul, Volume 14, Number 1 (Box 13, Folder 24)
    13th anniversary issue
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 14, Number 2, 1979 May 14 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 14, Number 3, 1979 May 28 (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - Soul, Volume 14, Number 4 (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - Soul (MAGIC AM Edition), Volume 14, Number 5, 1979 June 25 (Box 13, Folder 28)
  - Soul, Volume 14, Number 6, 1979 July 9 (Box 13, Folder 29)
  - Soul (MAGIC AM Edition), Volume 14, Number 7 (Box 13, Folder 30)
  - Soul, Volume 14, Number 8 (Box 13, Folder 31)
    "The Doobie Brothers: major White force invades Black music"
  - Soul (KKTT AM Edition), Volume 14, Number 9, 1979 August 20 (Box 13, Folder 32)
    "Michael at 21" [Michael Jackson]
  - Soul (KKTT AM Edition), Volume 14, Number 10, 1979 September 17 (Box 13, Folder 33)
  - Soul, Volume 14, Number 11 (Box 13, Folder 34)
  - Soul, Volume 14, Number 12, 1979 November 12 (Box 13, Folder 35)
  - Soul, Volume 14, Number 13, 1979 December 24 (Box 13, Folder 36)
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 14, Number 14 (Box 13, Folder 37)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 14, Number 15 (Box 13, Folder 38)
  - Soul (KGFJ Edition), Volume 14, Number 16, 1980 March (Box 13, Folder 39)
  - Soul (THE SOUL Edition), Volume 14, Number 17, 1980 April (Box 13, Folder 40)
    "Is disco dying? Disco producers and artists speak out"
  - Soul (THE SOUL Edition), Volume 15, Number 1 (Box 13, Folder 41)
    14th anniversary issue
  - Soul (KDIA Edition), Volume 15, Number 2, 1980 June (Box 13, Folder 42)
  - Soul, Volume 15, Number 3, 1980 July (Box 13, Folder 43)
  - Soul, Volume 15, Number 4 (Box 13, Folder 44)
  - Soul (K-ACE LOS ANGELES Edition), Volume 15, Number 5, 1980 September (Box 13, Folder 45)
  - Soul, Volume 15, Number 6, 1980 October (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Soul (K-ACE LOS ANGELES Edition), Volume 15, Number 7 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Soul (K-ACE LOS ANGELES Edition), Volume 15, Number 8 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Soul, Volume 15, Number 9, 1981 March/April (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Soul, Volume 16, Number 1, 1981 May/June (Box 14, Folder 5)
    15th anniversary issue
  - Soul, Volume 16, Number 2 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Soul, Volume 16, Number 3, 1981 September/October (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Soul, Volume 16, Number 4, 1981 November (Box 14, Folder 8)
    "Special collectors' edition, Diana: the untold story"
  - Soul, Volume 16, Number 5 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Soul, Volume 16, Number 6, 1982 January (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Soul Magazine, Volume 15, Number 7, 1982 March/April (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Soul Magazine, Volume 16, Number 1 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    16th anniversary issue
  - Soul (KGFJ Soul), Volume 1, Bound Issues, 1966 April 14-1967 March 30 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Soul, Volume 3, Bound Issues, 1968 May 6-1969 May 5 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Soul, Volume 7, Bound Issues (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Soul, Volume 8, Bound Issues, 1973 April 23-1974 April 15 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Soul, Volume 9, Bound Issues, 1974 April 29-1975 April 14 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Soul, Volumes 1-3, Microfilm (Box 77, Folder 10)
    Microfilm of Soul Newspaper issues
  - Soul, Volumes 4-7, Microfilm, 1969 May 19-1972 December 18 (Box 77, Folder 11)
- 2. Research Files, 1955-2002
  Newspaper and magazine clippings, press releases, correspondence, interview transcripts, article drafts, concert programs, posters, and other promotional materials.
  - Miscellaneous A, ca. 1989-1997 (Box 17, Folder 1)
  - Paula Abdul (Box 17, Folder 2)
  - Ewart Abner, ca. 1973-1975 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    See also Motown, box 39, folders 1-6
  - Muhammad Ali -- general, ca. 1973-1979 (Box 17, Folder 4)
  - Muhammad Ali -- books (Box 17, Folder 5)
  - Muhammad Ali -- boxing data, ca. 1967-1979 (Box 17, Folder 6)
  - Muhammad Ali -- Cassius Clay, ca. 1968-1976 (Box 17, Folder 7)
  - Muhammad Ali -- George Foreman (Box 17, Folder 8)
  - Muhammad Ali -- Antonio Inoki (Box 17, Folder 9)
  - Muhammad Ali -- lawyers, ca. 1971-1975 (Box 17, Folder 10)
  - Muhammad Ali -- manager, ca. 1976 (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Muhammad Ali -- Buster Mathis (Box 17, Folder 12)
  - Muhammad Ali -- movies (Box 17, Folder 13)
  - Muhammad Ali -- Muhammad Ali Day, ca. 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 14)
  - Muhammad Ali -- Muhammad Ali Invitational Track Meet, ca. 1977 (Box 17, Folder 15)
  - Muhammad Ali -- Muslim religion (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Muhammad Ali -- Ken Norton (Box 17, Folder 17)
  - Muhammad Ali -- recording business, ca. 1973-1977 (Box 17, Folder 18)
  - Muhammad Ali -- the self promoter, ca. 1971-1979 (Box 17, Folder 19)
  - Muhammad Ali -- Soul Newspaper (Box 17, Folder 20)
    Comprised primarily of Soul Newspaper clippings
  - Muhammad Ali -- televisio, ca. 1971-1979 (Box 17, Folder 21)
  - Muhammad Ali -- training camp, ca. 1967-1978 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - Muhammad Ali -- Chuck Wepner (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Muhammad Ali -- with others, ca. 1968-1977 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Muhammad Ali -- wives, ca. 1968-1977 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Debbie Allen (Box 18, Folder 5)
    Also known as Deborah Allen
  - Herb Alpert, ca. 1978 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - Ashford & Simpson, ca. 1971-1980 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Cholly Atkins (Box 18, Folder 8)
    It appears that Cholly Atkins also went by Charlie Atkins
  - Miscellaneous B, ca. 1988-1998 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - Pearl Bailey, ca. 1965-1979 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Josephine Baker (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Fontella Bass, ca. 1966-1977 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Shirley Bassey, ca. 1966-1978 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - Harry Belafonte (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - Archie Bell (Box 19, Folder 1)
  - Blinky, ca. 1968-1974 (Box 19, Folder 2)
    Blinky is also known as "Blinky Williams"
  - Book of Numbers, ca. 1973 (Box 19, Folder 3)
  - Toni Braxton (Box 19, Folder 4)
  - Brenda and the Tabulations, ca. 1977 (Box 19, Folder 5)
  - Johnny Bristol, ca. 1972-1979 (Box 19, Folder 6)
  - Bobby Brown (Box 19, Folder 7)
    See also Whitney Houston, box 27, folder 22; box 28, folders 1-11; box 29, folders 1-6; and box 30, folders 1-4
  - James Brown -- general, ca. 1968-1997 (Box 19, Folder 8)
  - James Brown -- David Bowie, ca. 1975-1978 (Box 19, Folder 9)
  - Jim Brown (Box 19, Folder 10)
  - Peabo Bryson, ca. 1977-1980 (Box 19, Folder 11)
  - Jerry Butler, ca. 1966-1986 (Box 19, Folder 12)
  - G. C. Cameron (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Mariah Carey (Box 19, Folder 14)
    See also Whitney Houston, box 29, folder 4 for articles addressing comparisons
  - Judy Carne, ca. 1985-1986 (Box 19, Folder 15)
  - Diahann Carroll, ca. 1965-1997 (Box 19, Folder 16)
    See also Julia, box 33, folder 3; Claudine, box 20, folder 7
  - Mel Carter (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Chairmen of the Board, ca. 1970-1977 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Chubby Checker, ca. 1974-1977 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Chee Chee and Peppy (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Chic (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - The Chiffons, ca. 1975-1976 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Claudine, ca. 1974-1975 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    See also Diahann Carroll, box 19, folder 16
  - Natalie Cole (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Nat King Cole, ca. 1966-1976 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Comedy Store, ca. 1979-1988 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - The Commodores (Box 20, Folder 11)
    See also Lionel Ritchie, box 44, folder 1
  - The Contours, ca. 1966-1974 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Marc Copage, ca. 1969-1978 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    See also Julia, box 33, folder 3
  - Bill Cosby -- general (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Bill Cosby -- son's death, ca. 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Miscellaneous D, ca. 1986-1998 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Dorothy Dandridge (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Sarah Dash (Box 21, Folder 2)
    See also Labelle, box 35, folders 7-8
  - Angela Davis, ca. 1969-1978 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Betty Davis, ca. 1973-1977 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Billy Davis and Marilyn McCoo (Box 21, Folder 5)
    See also Fifth Dimension, box 21, folders 1-4, and Marilyn McCoo, box 37, folder 6
  - Dawn, ca. 1973-1978 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Suzanne de Passe, ca. 1968-1989 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - DeBarge (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Delfonics, ca. 1968-1976 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - The Dells, ca. 1968-1977 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - The Dixie Cups (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Carol Douglas, ca. 1974-1976 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - The Dramatics, ca. 1971-1978 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - The Dramatics and Ron Banks (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - The Drifters (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Dynamic Superiors, ca. 1973-1977 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Dennis Edwards, ca. 1968-1977 (Box 21, Folder 17)
    See also Temptations, box 49, folders 6-8 and box 50, folders 1-4
  - Earth, Wind & Fire -- general (Box 22, Folder 1)
    See also Maurice White, box 52, folder 3
  - Earth, Wind & Fire -- feature articles, ca. 1973-1979 (Box 22, Folder 2)
  - Bill Elliott (Box 22, Folder 3)
    See also Dionne Warwick -- Bill Elliott, box 51, folder 17
  - Emotions (folder 1 of 2) (Box 22, Folder 4)
  - Emotions (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1973-1997 (Box 22, Folder 5)
  - En Vogue, ca. 1992-1994 (Box 22, Folder 6)
  - Betty Everett (Box 22, Folder 7)
  - Miscellaneous F (Box 22, Folder 8)
  - Lola Falana, ca. 1970-1979 (Box 22, Folder 9)
  - Fifth Dimension -- general (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1968-1976 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    Primarily contains information related to original lineup; see also Billy Davis and Marilyn McCoo, box 21, folder 5; Marilyn McCoo, box 37, folder 6
  - Fifth Dimension -- general (folder 2 of 2) (Box 23, Folder 2)
    Includes a few clippings under the group's former name, the Versatiles
  - Fifth Dimension -- New Fifth Dimension, ca. 1975-1977 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    Includes information related to the group after the departures of Billy Davis and Marilyn McCoo
  - Fifth Dimension -- New Fifth Dimension -- Eloise Laws, ca. 1976-1977 (Box 23, Folder 4)
  - First Choice (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - Roberta Flack, ca. 1970-1980 (Box 23, Folder 6)
  - Four Tops, ca. 1966-1982 (Box 23, Folder 7)
  - Aretha Franklin -- general (folder 1 of 4) (Box 23, Folder 8)
    Includes a few clippings relating to Michael Peterson, "Mr. Aretha Franklin"
  - Aretha Franklin -- general (folder 2 of 4), ca. 1967-1998 (Box 24, Folder 1)
  - Aretha Franklin -- general (folder 3 of 4), ca. 1967-1996 (Box 24, Folder 2)
  - Aretha Franklin -- general (folder 3 of 4) (Box 24, Folder 3)
  - Aretha Franklin -- biography, ca. 1987-1989 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    Correspondence regarding use of Soul staffer J. Randy Taraborrelli's photographs of Aretha Franklin for biography by Mark Bego
  - Carolyn Franklin, ca. 1969-1976 (Box 24, Folder 5)
  - Melvin Franklin (Box 24, Folder 6)
  - Friends of Distinction, ca. 1969-1974 (Box 24, Folder 7)
  - The Fuzz, ca. 1970 (Box 24, Folder 8)
  - Miscellaneous G (Box 24, Folder 9)
  - Gloria Gaynor, ca. 1975-1996 (Box 24, Folder 10)
  - Marla Gibbs, ca. 1977-1979 (Box 25, Folder 1)
  - Kathie Lee Gifford (Box 25, Folder 2)
  - Whoopi Goldberg (Box 25, Folder 3)
  - Berry Gordy, Jr. -- general (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1967-1997 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    See also Motown, box 39, folders 1-6 and box 40, folders 1-3; Gordy 1994 -- Taraborrelli research, box 56, folder 10; Motown 1994 -- Taraborrelli research, box 56, folder 11
  - Berry Gordy, Jr. -- general (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1966-1990 (Box 25, Folder 5)
  - Berry Gordy, Jr. -- 1970s (Box 25, Folder 6)
  - Berry Gordy, Jr. -- 1980s, ca. 1980-1989 (Box 25, Folder 7)
  - Berry Gordy, Jr. -- Berry Gordy's The Last Dragon, ca. 1985 (Box 25, Folder 8)
  - Gordy family (Box 25, Folder 9)
  - Lou Gossett, Jr. (Box 26, Folder 1)
  - Kelsey Grammer, ca. 1989-1997 (Box 26, Folder 2)
  - Al Green -- general, ca. 1972-1978 (Box 26, Folder 3)
  - Al Green -- Mary Woodson (Box 26, Folder 4)
  - Susaye and Viviane Greene (Box 26, Folder 5)
  - Richard Grieco, ca. 1992 (Box 26, Folder 6)
  - Bryant Gumbel, ca. 1994 (Box 26, Folder 7)
  - Arsenio Hall (Box 26, Folder 8)
  - Deidre Hall (Box 26, Folder 9)
  - Hall & Oates, ca. 1975-1978 (Box 26, Folder 10)
  - M.C. Hammer, ca. 1991 (Box 26, Folder 11)
  - George Harrison (Box 26, Folder 12)
  - Phil Hartman -- death (Box 26, Folder 13)
  - Goldie Hawn, ca. 1982-1998 (Box 26, Folder 14)
  - Isaac Hayes -- general (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1969-1977 (Box 26, Folder 15)
  - Isaac Hayes -- general (folder 2 of 2) (Box 26, Folder 16)
  - Isaac Hayes -- The New Isaac Hayes (Box 27, Folder 1)
  - Isaac Hayes -- Dionne Warwick, ca. 1976-1978 (Box 27, Folder 2)
  - Lloyd Haynes, ca. 1969-1975 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    See also Room 222, box 44, folder 5
  - Rita Hayworth (Box 27, Folder 4)
  - Joey Heatherton, ca. 1986 (Box 27, Folder 5)
  - Nona Hendryx, ca. 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 6)
  - Katharine Hepburn (Box 27, Folder 7)
  - Charlton Heston, ca. 1986 (Box 27, Folder 8)
  - High Inergy, ca. 1977-1978 (Box 27, Folder 9)
  - The Hamiltons (Box 27, Folder 10)
  - Hines, Hines, and Dad (Box 27, Folder 11)
  - Dustin Hoffman, ca. 1985 (Box 27, Folder 12)
  - Billie Holiday, ca. 1957-1986 (Box 27, Folder 13)
  - Holland-Dozier-Holland -- general (Box 27, Folder 14)
    See also Invictus Records, box 31, folder 2
  - Holland-Dozier-Holland -- Lamont Dozier, ca. 1974-1986 (Box 27, Folder 15)
    Contains information about Lamont Dozier's solo career
  - Brenda Holloway, ca. 1967-1976 (Box 27, Folder 16)
    Also includes items relating to Patrice Holloway
  - Honeycone (Box 27, Folder 17)
    See also Edna Wright, box 54, folder 4
  - Bob Hope, ca. 1983-1988 (Box 27, Folder 18)
  - Lena Horne, ca. 1968-1997 (Box 27, Folder 19)
  - Cissy Houston (Box 27, Folder 20)
  - Thelma Houston, ca. 1966-1983 (Box 27, Folder 21)
  - Whitney Houston -- general (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1991-1998 (Box 27, Folder 22)
    See also Bobby Brown, box 19, folder 7
  - Whitney Houston -- general (folder 2 of 2) (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - Whitney Houston -- book deal, ca. 1986-1998 (Box 28, Folder 2)
  - Whitney Houston -- captions, ca. 1994 (Box 28, Folder 3)
  - Whitney Houston -- Steve Ivory original chapters (Box 28, Folder 4)
  - Whitney Houston -- P.I. reports, ca. 1992-1995 (Box 28, Folder 5)
  - Whitney Houston -- used articles, ca. 1989-1998 (Box 28, Folder 6)
  - Whitney Houston -- feature stories (folder 1 of 2) (Box 28, Folder 7)
  - Whitney Houston -- feature stories (folder 2 of 2) (Box 28, Folder 8)
  - Whitney Houston -- 1982-1984, ca. 1982-1984 (Box 28, Folder 9)
  - Whitney Houston -- 1985, ca. 1985 (Box 28, Folder 10)
  - Whitney Houston -- 1986 (Box 28, Folder 11)
  - Whitney Houston -- 1987 (Box 29, Folder 1)
  - Whitney Houston -- 1988, ca. 1988 (Box 29, Folder 2)
  - Whitney Houston -- 1989, ca. 1989 (Box 29, Folder 3)
  - Whitney Houston -- 1990 (Box 29, Folder 4)
  - Whitney Houston -- 1991 (Box 29, Folder 5)
  - Whitney Houston -- 1992, ca. 1992 (Box 29, Folder 6)
  - Whitney Houston -- 1993 (folder 1 of 2), ca. 1993 (Box 30, Folder 1)
  - Whitney Houston -- 1993 (folder 2 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 2)
  - Whitney Houston -- 1994 (folder 1 of 2) (Box 30, Folder 3)
  - Whitney Houston -- 1994 (folder 2 of 2), ca. 1994 (Box 30, Folder 4)
  - Engelbert Humperdinck, ca. 1987-1988 (Box 30, Folder 5)
  - Willie Hutch (Box 30, Folder 6)
  - Phyllis Hyman (Box 30, Folder 7)
  - Impact of Brass, ca. 1970-1972 (Box 30, Folder 8)
  - The Imperials, ca. 1976-1979 (Box 30, Folder 9)
    The group was previously known as Little Anthony and the Imperials
  - The Impressions (Box 31, Folder 1)
    See also Curtis Mayfield, box 37, folder 4
  - Invictus Records, ca. 1969-1976 (Box 31, Folder 2)
    See also Holland-Dozier-Holland, box 27, folders 14-15
  - Isley Brothers, ca. 1969-1979 (Box 31, Folder 3)
  - Miscellaneous J (Box 31, Folder 4)
  - Jesse Jackson, ca. 1969-1978 (Box 31, Folder 5)
  - Michael Jackson, ca. 2002 (Box 31, Folder 6)
    Issue of Vibe Magazine with article written by Soul publisher Regina Jones; see also Quincy Jones, box 32, folder 14 for articles about Thriller and Michael Jackson turning 30; Motown...the Wiz?
  - Millie Jackson (Box 31, Folder 7)
  - Jackson Five, ca. 1974 (Box 31, Folder 8)
  - Lawrence-Hilton Jacobs, ca. 1975-1979 (Box 31, Folder 9)
  - Mick Jagger (Box 32, Folder 1)
    See also Rolling Stones, box 44, folder 4
  - Etta James, ca. 1968-1978 (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - Joni James, ca. 1997 (Box 32, Folder 3)
  - Rick James (Box 32, Folder 4)
    See also Teena Marie, box 36, folder 16
  - Rick James and the Stone City Band, ca. 1979-1983 (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Billy Joel, ca. 1978-1990 (Box 32, Folder 6)
  - Elton John (Box 32, Folder 7)
  - Don Johnson, ca. 1986-1998 (Box 32, Folder 8)
  - Magic Johnson, ca. 1994 (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Etta Jones (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Grace Jones (Box 32, Folder 11)
  - Ken Jones, ca. 1970-1978 (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Tom Jones, ca. 1969-1984 (Box 32, Folder 13)
  - Quincy Jones (folder 1 of 2) (Box 32, Folder 14)